Hello everyone welcome to India stock
market so gas today we will talk about
research on ICC Lombard quarter
but before that you must subscribe to my channel,
like, comment,
share and yes don't forget to press the bell icon and
give your love so let's learn something new today so
gas today we will talk about research on ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company the
fundamentals of the company are very strong the company's
financials are also a good stock a
short term delivery you have to buy ok let's buy
ok so gas ICC Lombard current market
price
178.15 with price you
have to buy current market price
5.5 share
ICC Lombard General Insurance
reported a net profit of ₹437 crore in the
quarter of
March
this is an increase of 40% from Rs
46 crore
₹47 crore in the fourth quarter compare
with Rs 3973 crore and the
company has seen
growth in its income from investment
at Rs 616 crore
50038 crore in the last quarter  OK The
Group Direct Premium Income of GTPL
OK of the company stood at Rs ₹4977 crore
in the fourth quarter against Rs
₹466 crore in the same period last year, registering a
growth of 6.7%
.  Okay
members of the company
okay the interest on investment with their release
against you have come down by 1.08% during the
January-March period, 2.34% in the
presenting quarter and 0.41% in the previous
quarter on Thursday ahead of the result
ICC Lombard share close near 3% higher at
Rs
136.90 on the National Stock Exchange so for
this share this stock has slumped by 9%
Okay so as ICC Lombard quarterly
results have increased by 40% to
Rs 437 crore dividend should be declared at 5.50% the
company has declared share dividend at 5.50
then please allow Namaste say Radhe
Radhe